# 胸口碎大石
Breaking rocks on the chest
# 最近我老弟跟我说
Recently, my brother said
# 天天电焊做东西
We've been welding stuff every day
# 累得跟孙子一样
making us as tired as hell
# 能不能选个别的活
Can we find some other work to do
# 躺着而且非常爷们地就能赚到钱
so that we can just lie down and earn money in a manly way
# 我感觉有一种职业没准能行
I feel that there's a job that should work
# 那就是街头表演
which is street performance
# 胸口碎大石
Breaking rocks on the chest
# 躺着而且非常爷们
Lying and very masculine
# 但是我们没有练过，直接锤肯定不行
But we are not trained, so we can't just hammer it
# 要想完成表演需要一些道具
To finish the performance, we need some props
# 所以经过我们多日的研究制作和实验
Therefore, after researching, crafting and experimenting for many days
# 我们做了一个小铁背心
We've made this little iron vest
# 它能抵抗大部分的冲击力
It resists most of the impact
# 从而让我们安全表演节目而不受到伤害
so that we can perform safely without injuries
# 表演的时候外面套一个外套就可以了
When performing, just wear a coat to cover it
# 但是
However
# 我感觉光做到这些还不够
I feel like this is not enough
# 为了吸引人流
To attract the crowd
# 和增加视觉效果
and to enhance the visual effects
# 一把炫酷拉风的锤子是必不可少的
A cool fancy hammer is necessary
# 所以
Therefore
# 我做了一把变形金刚式的大锤
I made a big Transformers style hammer
# 它的锤头像个大黄蜂的轮子
The head looks like a wheel of Bumblebee
# 非常的漂亮
Very beautiful
# 可以看到
As you can see
# 而且
Besides
# 看这里有个按钮
Look, we have a button here
# 上面有一个音箱
There's a speaker here
# 还可以有一种音乐打点的效果
which gives the idea of music beating
# 我给大家试一下
Let me show you guys
# （八十！）
(Eighty!)
# 而且插上电源安上轮子之后
And after plugging in and installing the wheels
# 它可以变成一个代步工具
It becomes a method of transportation
# 试一下
Let me try
# 可以拐弯
We can make a turn
# 这样你表演完以后就可以骑着锤子回家
So after performing, you can ride your hammer home
# 你这是骑了个什么？
What are you riding?
# 骑个锤子
I'm riding a hammer
# 一切准备就绪
Everything ready
# 下面给大家表演一下
Now let's perform
# 由于找不到石头
Since we can't find a rock
# 自己注了块水泥演示一下
I made this piece of cement to show you
# 危险动作，千万不要模仿
Dangerous, do not ever imitate
# 准备好了吗老弟
Are you ready, brother?
# 准备好了
Ready
# 怎么样老弟
How is that, brother?
# 一点事都没有，非常成功
Absolutely no problems, a huge success
# 如果以后你看到我们哥俩拿着这个锤子在街头表演
If you ever spot the two of us performing on streets with this hammer
# 希望你们能够支持一下
I hope you can support us
# 谢谢
Thank you
# 以前做的一个可穿戴式拍摄稳定器
This is a wearable video stabilizer
# 因为怕你们说有用取关我
I was afraid you will unfollow me for this being useful
# 也没敢发视频
So I didn't dare to upload the video
# 但是最近比较热也没什么好的想法
But it's quite hot recently, and I've run out of ideas
# 让它先 tang 一下吧 （没听明白是什么字）
So let's give it a shot
# 我给你们大家介绍一下
I'll introduce it to you guys
# 先把这个固定在身上
First, fix this to your body
# 这样
Like this
# 再把悬臂安装上
Then install the arm
# 然后再把支架拧上就可以了
And finally install the rack, then it's done
# 这样就安装完成了
Now the installation is complete
# 它可以让你同时轻松地多手机直播或者是拍摄
It allows you streaming or filming with multiple phones at the same time with ease
# 不像以前那么累
Not as tiring as before
# 还可以调节角度
We can also adjust the angle
# 像这样
Like this
# 感谢收看 欢迎订阅
# —— 手工耿
Thanks for watching, please subscribe
-- Handicraft Geng